Hello everyone. Welcome back to today's another new tutorial topic. So today I'll create the MongoDB
validation using the information on the MongoDB shared. In this session, we will perfectly explain
improved data integrity, constancy by seeking validation rules for the MongoDB collections.
So here I can just start for segment and first of all connecting for my database. First of all,
in this session, I'm just starting newly create the new collection. So here in this session,
first of all, here I can type the DB, then type simply just type here the create the grid
collection, where I can prepare the parenthesis, the double quotation, instead create for the collection
may appone, suppose like when not picture. Okay. So now I define for non-fiction perfectly now,
here press enter and you can see this database is already now created. Okay. So now just go for
then here the DB. Okay. So just go for inside is not here. So here today, so just see here I can create
for perfectly open for the students for the fiction to the collection. Okay. And I hope you
understand this. And next up here, the collection and just describe this is the show, the collections.
So basically, you can see the all the collections documents and the non-fiction. So to design perfectly,
you can understand it. So now here, I create for the collections for some
first of all, I can define for the show collection here, I can insert for on first of all, the DB.
Here, DB dot type the non-fiction and finally, perfectly find the non-fiction dot here,
service like this is the insert one. Okay. And in this insert, first of all, I can type the
parenthesis also create the value brackets defined for the name. So here is for the name,
suppose like A, B, C. Okay. Now here, perfectly created and
best enter and you can see perfectly created this option. And here is for another option.
Now here, the data here, I can define for the data search. So I can just type the DB
dot here is friction dot here, describe insert one. And here, first of all, I can type for
this is the name used for suppose like for here inside randomly used for three, four, five, six, seven,
eight, nine. Okay. So three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, completely done. And you can see
the completely created for the acknowledgement and true and the certain name. And here,
perfectly created name. And now just go for here and show this function and type the DB dot
the non-fiction dot here. I can use the defined function and they'll see for all the records.
So you can see here perfectly inside the perfect loop within the condition. Okay. So we can
further understand it. Now here, create for the non-fiction. So I can just go here and first
code here, I can create simply. So define the code here, the simply just paste the object. So
here, I can define simply just create for the corrections. So now in this JSON create data. So now
here, I can open for the base code and here, I have already created for the data segment and
just I can copy. Okay. So just copy and then paste for here. Because so now here paste and you
can see here completely pasted this and now here, simply trying for interpolation, you can see
here the Mongo DB and now directly. So now here, and simply first create the document. So first of all,
I can define for the DB dot here, I can just try the create. So first of all, create the collection.
And in this inside, first of all, I can create for the parent sees the double
quotation incidentally, I can create supposedly the non-fiction. Okay. And also create here
the curly brackets and now here, I can create for just simply the double quotation. Okay.
So now the double quotation and here, the double query. Okay. So simply now this inside,
we can select here. So first of all, I can just again, create the copy and paste here. And now
now here, I can again paste for this data. And here, it is completely done perfectly. I'll create
this code for, you can choose for here, you can create for the non-fiction insights, just use
or choose for create for the insights of the book. Okay. So now just go for here and I can
import from the book. So here, first of all, I can understand, define for the syntax process. So first
type the db dot here, you can type the non-fiction. Okay. Then go use for here, simply type the insert.
Okay. So insert and here, this place, the parent sees and also print the curly brackets. So
here, first of all, I can define for the name. And here, first of all, name the book name for here,
the way of man. Okay. And next step here, we can type here the price. Okay. So different for
the price column. So here, I use for the blocking point, but this symbol and here, use for the
price is 300 or 20. Okay. So you can see here, just press the enter and you can see the result
of the MongoDB successful query. Okay. And you can process this completely done. And I hope
you've got to understand and here, I have completely tried the process and completely working.
And I hope you've got to understand the session. So thank you for watching and happy coding.